Foundation for Child Development records, Accession 2012:052 FA421
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1; 16.4 Cubic Feet
  - School of the 21st Century
    - 1997 (Box 31, Folder 296)
  - Schott Center for Public and Early Education, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 297)
  - SSRC: Lenzer: Discretionary, 1992-1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 298)
  - The Social Workers National Research and Education Fund, Inc., 1994-1997 (Box 31, Folder 299)
  - Society for Research in Child Development, 1995-1999, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 300)
  - SECA: Little Rock, Arkansas, 2000-2001 (Box 32, Folder 301)
  - The Southern Institute on Children and Families, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 302)
  - State Communities Aid Association
    - 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 303)
    - Child Health Crisis Start. Group - Discretionary, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 304)
  - SUNY Rockefeller Institute of Government: JOBS Program Evaluation, 1990-1994 (Box 32, Folder 305)
  - Statewide Youth Advocacy, Inc.
    - 1992-1995 (Box 32, Folder 306)
    - Children's Budget Project, 1994-1997 (Box 32, Folder 307)
  - Teachers College/Columbia University
    - 1994-1997, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 308)
    - 1998-2000 (Box 32, Folder 309)
    - Neighborhood Research Grants Program - Brooks - Gunn, 1994-1999 (Box 32, Folder 310)
    - NYC Fellowship Program, 1992-1995 (Box 32, Folder 311)
    - Putting Children First - Discretionary, 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 312)
  - Third Street Music School Settlement, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 313)
  - The Tides Center
    - Children's Partnership, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 314)
    - Grantmakers for Education, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 315)
    - Grantmakers Income Security Task Force, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 316)
  - The Tides Foundation
    - ACT - Part 1, 1994-1996 (Box 33, Folder 317)
    - ACT - Part 2, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 318)
    - City Connect, 1994-1996 (Box 33, Folder 319)
    - City Connect, 1996-1998 (Box 33, Folder 320)
    - Grantmakers for Children, Youth, & Families, 1994-1997 (Box 33, Folder 321)
    - Grantmakers Income Security Task Force, 1994-1996 (Box 33, Folder 322)
    - 1997-1999 (Box 33, Folder 323)
  - Tufts University, Trustees of
    - 1996-1998 (Box 33, Folder 324)
    - 1998-2000 (Box 33, Folder 325)
    - Nutrition - Cognition Initiative - Discretionary, 1993-1995 (Box 33, Folder 326)
  - Unitarian Universalist Service Committee, 1998-2001 (Box 33, Folder 327)
  - United Fund of Greater NY: Minority Foster Care Development, Discretionary, 1992-1995 (Box 34, Folder 328)
  - United Hospital Fund, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 329)
  - US Committee for UNICEF: Children's Week in NYC, Discretionary, 1990-1993 (Box 34, Folder 330)
  - United Way of NYC
    - 1995-1997 (Box 34, Folder 331)
    - Minority Foster Care Project - Discretionary, 1993-1997 (Box 34, Folder 332)
  - United Way of NY State, 1995-1997 (Box 34, Folder 333)
  - University at Albany Fund, Inc., 1992-1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 334)
  - University of Chicago
    - Chapin Hall Center for Children, 1989-1992 (Box 34, Folder 335)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 34, Folder 336)
    - Irving B. Harris School of Public Policy, 1998-2000 (Box 34, Folder 337)
    - State of the Child, 1987-1992 (Box 34, Folder 338)
  - University of Illinois, 1999-2003 (Box 34, Folder 339)
  - University of Massachusetts Medical Center: Discretionary Symposium, 1993-1996 (Box 34, Folder 340)
  - The University of Michigan
    - 1995-1996 (Box 34, Folder 341)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 35, Folder 342)
    - Society for Research on Adolescence, 1991, 1995, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 343)
  - UNC @ Chapel Hill, 1997-2000 (Box 35, Folder 344)
  - University of Pennsylvania, Trustees of, 1997-1998, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 345)
  - University of Rochester, 1999-2000 (Box 35, Folder 346)
  - The University of South Carolina: National Black Family Summit, Discretionary, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 347)
  - University of Washington, 1995-1997 (Box 35, Folder 348)
  - University of Wisconsin
    - 1994-1996 (Box 35, Folder 349)
    - Madison - Discretionary, 1992-1993, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 350)
    - Madison School of Social Work, 1996-1997 (Box 35, Folder 351)
  - University Settlement Society of NY, 1995-1997 (Box 35, Folder 352)
  - University System of George
    - Neighborhood Research Grants Program - Abbott - Shim, 1993-1996 (Box 35, Folder 353)
    - Neighborhood Research Grants Program: Elifson, 1993-1995 (Box 35, Folder 354)
  - The Urban Institute
    - Conference on Welfare Reform, 1993-1996 (Box 35, Folder 355)
    - Gathering and Dissemination of Information on FSA, 1989-1992 (Box 35, Folder 356)
    - Transition from Welfare to Work, 1994-1996 (Box 36, Folder 357)
    - Part 1-2, 1998-1999 (Box 36, Folder 358)
  - Victim Services, 1996-1997 (Box 36, Folder 359)
  - Wheelock College
    - Part 1, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Folder 360)
    - Part 2, 1998-1999 (Box 36, Folder 361)
    - Part 3, 1998-2000 (Box 36, Folder 362)
    - 1998-2001 (Box 36, Folder 363)
  - Women and Foundation: Corporate Philanthropy, 1994-1996 (Box 36, Folder 364)
  - Women and Philanthropy, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 365)
  - Yale University, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 366)
  - Yale University: Bush Center in Child Development and Social Policy, 2000-2001 (Box 37, Folder 367)
- Board of Directors, 2; 0.1 Cubic Feet
  - Foundation for Child Development: Board of Directors and Council Minutes, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 368)